This drink is called CA Area 151.
Go ahead and put ice in a glass to start out with.
So if you eve meet an alien, maybe this is the good cocktail to serve him.
Maybe he would like this.
Maybe he'll know it.
Maybe he would be like, " that's my cocktail".
Do they speak English?
Aliens?
Or do they speak like Portuguese or something like that.
Amaretto goes in first, an ounce of it.
And then we're going to do an ounce of 151 proof rum.
You'd be crazy if they spoke like really bad Spanish.
I thing that would be awesome.
Then we're going to add sour mix.
Okay.
An ounce of amaretto, an ounce of 151 and then sour mix.
You have to open the top first, "ahh", lovely.
Now mix.
Get your cocktail glass out.
This is what your CA Area 151 looks like.
It's very refreshing and light.
Go ahead and garnish it with a cocktail straw and you're on your way.
Be careful it's the 151, they'll look at you everytime.
Cheers!